BRYAN K. MUNOZ

(707) 360-8513 \$\displaysum \text{bryank.munoz@gmail.com} \$\displaysum \text{linkedin.com/in/bryan-k-munoz}\$

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering - Computer Systems

2016 - 2020

University of California, Santa Cruz - Jack Baskin School of Engineering

GPA: 3.0

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Pragmatic and motivated Software Engineer experienced with various programming languages and hardware components. Detail oriented, as demonstrated by advanced university coursework involving computer systems, and highly personable after providing professional customer service over multiple years.

TECHNICAL STRENGTHS

Programming Languages

C 4yrs , C++ 4yrs , Java 2yrs , (JavaScript CSS HTML) 1yr , Python 1yr

Digital Logic Design Stack Components Verilog (Structural and Behavioral) 3yrs Node.js, Express, ReactJS, HTML

Development Tools Gith Operating Systems Win

Github, LaTeX, MatLab, VirtualBox, WordPress, Vivado, PSoC Creator

Windows, Linux

PROJECTS

Wi-Fi Probing Population Monitor

github.com/UCSC-CSE123/beavertail

Capstone Project

- · A tool to inexpensively measure population within a 150ft radius using only a microcontroller and wifi adaptor.
- \cdot Worked on collecting and processing WiFi probe request data using Python.
- · Designed a method to confidently deduce the number of smartphones within WiFi range using MAC Addresses and RSSI values.
- · Remotely coordinated and collaborated with a team of five engineers using Slack and GitHub.

Audio Synthesizer

github.com/bryan-kenneth/audio-synthesizer

Logic Design Project

- · Created an interface to generate audio waves for the CODEC chip on an FPGA.
- · On-board switches control which digitally generated waves are superimposed/simultaneously active.
- · Integrated adjustable frequency and volume controls using debounced buttons.

Oscilloscope

github.com/bryan-kenneth/oscilloscope

Microcontroller Project

- · Created a dual-channel oscilloscope using two microcontrollers (PSoC5 and RPI).
- · Utilized PSoC5 for capturing ADC samples and sending data via USB.
- · Programmed RPI to process and visualize signals through on-board HDMI using OpenVG.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bodega Bay Lodge

Nov 2020 - Present

Front Desk Agent

· High level guest services while navigating a property management system

Lucas Wharf Restaurant

2015 - 2019

Server

· Fast paced work environment in which communication, teamwork, and multitasking are essential tools

Bodega Bay Public Utilities, Intern

Jan 2016 - May 2016

Site Engineer

· On-site civil engineering internship focused on water testing & treatment infrastructure